

# Mohammad Shamsi

**Back-end Developer** Mobile Application Developer



🕑 Tehran, Tehran Province, Iran **(**+98) 9176509634

I developed a particular interest in programming during my undergraduate studies at the Computer Engineering dept., The Kermanshah University of Technology. After graduation, I worked as a freelancer for two years as an android developer. Since 2020, I have been a Mobile Application Developer and Backend Developer at Domil.io Co. My experiences made me good at independent work and teamwork.







# Work Experience



January 2022 - Present

In January 2022, with good experience as a mobile developer, I started a Back-end Development Position in the same team, at Domil.io company. We worked for different products in a consistent business-to-business structure. During this time, I have improved my skills and knowledge and had many interesting experiences.

#### Mobile Application Developer • Domil.io Ħ

July 2020 - January 2022

In July 2020, I started my internship as a Mobile Developer with Flutter framework. After three months, we created a new development team, and we started the Jeanswest Store Application Project.

After one year and 7 months, due to personal interests and team needs, I changed my stack to back-end Development.

# Android Developer • Freelance, self-employed

April 2017 - December 2018

In April 2017, at the same time as I started learning programming at the basic level, I found my interest in developing mobile applications.

# Freedonce Java Software Developer • Freelance, self-employed

April 2017 - December 2018

In April 2017, I started programming with C++ and Java, as a self-taught university academic. I used to do very small and amateur projects on a part-time basis.

# Full-Time Projects



# Jeanswest Mobile App.

Jeanswest Mobile Application powered by Flutter(Dart)



# Jeanswest Application

Development Backend of Jeanswest Web, Jeanswest Web Application powered by NodeJS

#### Website:

https://www.jeanswest.ir/

#### Google Play Application:

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.avakatan.club&hl=en\_US&gl=US

### **Balcafe Website**



Development
Backend of Balcafe
Website powered by
NodeJS
https://balcafe.ir/



# Jeanswest STS (Saving Time Service)

Development Backend of Jeanswest STS Machine powered by NodeJS

#### **Project Introduction Video:**

https://drive.google.com/file/d
/1XyetIqvxwMljjSSrxksdAJ\_xXLYc5L
C6/view?usp=sharing

# Side-Projects

Flutter

# Minimal Farsi Whatsapp

created a very minimal Whatsapp in Farsi language with Flutter Technology. I worked with firebase, and Socket.io for chats, importing and exporting files from storage.

GitLab:

gitlab/whatsapp

Flutter



# Minimal Farsi Instagram

created a very minimal Instagram in Farsi language with Flutter Technology. I worked with Camera, QRCodes, and Profile Settings.

GitLab:

gitlab/insta\_farsi

Flutter



**Doctor App** 

Develop a mobile application for doctor appointments.

GitLab:

gitlab/doctor\_appointment

Flutter



Minimal UMDB App

Develop a mobile application for Information TV Shows from IMDb.

GitLab:

gitlab/umdb

# Education



Kermanshah University Of Technology

Bachelor's degree, Architecture System Computers

2013 - 2018

# **Skills**

